Good morning.
I'm going to set up the Onchi's kitchen now.
I'd like to set it up.
I heard that there is a member of One Love One Art
I heard there's a member of One Love One Art.
Where?
Oh, then, where are you?
Mr. Yoshizawa, welcome.
Good morning.
I'm sure you'll be a big success in your sleep.
Well, hello. Let's start with self-introductions.
Okay, over there.
Yes, I'm 19 years old. Good morning.
Yes, I'm 16 years old. I'm Yuusaki Miyu. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, I am Runo Izukawa.
Yes, I am Hirano Kiyobori.
Hirata?
Yes, I am Heike Heike
Yes, Hirano Masamon
Boiled Egg
Yes, hello, boiled egg.
I made Akinikuman.
Here, from here
Cross from here
Beamask?
Yes, this is Sakamori.
That's nice.
Hi, we're all together...
We're the "Old Imo Kozu"!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
We've already started the One Love One Heart event vlog.
Eh, event vlog
This is already a regular event.
This has become a regular event.
This is a milestone, and I'm going to be using the camera a lot.
Today is another day.
I want to know how everyone is doing at the event.
And Isshin?
When will Isshin put on his all-back hair?
This way, everyone.
What are you going to do this time?
That attention, I mean...
Yes, so let's cut it off for a moment.
Single-minded all-back
Okay, .
I'm fine. Well, I really, really, really want you to look for the all-back, so I'll do it this time.
I don't know, it might appear at the end because of some subliminal effect.
Please look at all of them slowly. Maybe only the thumbnail is all back.
How will it change from here?
Oh!
Today, Harumakun will also be wearing all back Yes, that's right Harumakun's bangs will be shortened by 2 cm today We'll see where it will be revealed today Do you know, Ayumu? , what do you mean ? , I'd like to do it. , what's going on? What do you mean? Today's hidden project, right? Yes, in the back. Well, I'd like to grow older one year at a time. How old are you?
How old are you? Today I'm going to add spikes to my hair one by one.
Today, we're looking for mistakes in this VLOG. Ah, I see. So, Anri is gradually turning into that, that, that boiled egg color.
, you're turning into a...
, so Yuna-chan's nails will grow 2 cm each , hahaha , 2 cm in one day today?
, and Mie-chan's singing voice keeps changing key and key... , huh... , gradually...
, you know, Ichi's coat is gradually turning gray , I see...
We're looking for mistakes in today's VLOG, so...
Well, let's all get fired up!
Let's do our best!
Let's close with A.A.O.
Seino
A.A.O.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
Come here, come here, come here.
oh!
Raise Event
Here we go.
Yes, sir.
This is the first time in our country.
I'm so excited...
, is it a kashira? You want to play? I've got to do it.
, yes, the base.
Yes, sir.
, don't let him get me!
, we have to make sure it's secure.
Yes, sir.
.
, steady!
Come on, keep your feet on the ground!
Well, if we don't have fun, the audience won't have fun either.
Let's put our worries aside for the moment.
Let's have fun today.
Yes, let's all go!
We are!
One for us!
Yes, this is where the story was first performed. How was everyone?
Thank you very much.
This is a song that encourages people to keep going without giving up, to give them a little push.
It has just been released and this is its first performance, so it's up to us to add color to the song, so let's keep up the good work!
Let's do our best! Please help us!
Three, two, one to Ichi's cute line.
Ichi is the cutest Ichi.
Isn't it tight? Isn't it tight?
Please use it here, too.
Then stop it. Cut it now.
You're the cutest, Ichi.
It was all there. Yuna's mouth.
It was all there.
It's totally fine.
Yes, today,
It's the first day of the shard album release event.
It's the first day.
Ebina is in Kanagawa.
That's right.
Let's land in Kanagawa.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is Miyu and Anri's home prefecture.
It's our home prefecture.
Nice to meet you. Good evening.
Good evening.
We would like to improve our performance a little more and update our performance with each release event.
We will do our best!
I'll do my best!
See you soon!
Thank you!
It feels different now, doesn't it?
I'll be back so much.
Wow! Really!
Thank you so much!
And again!
You're right, it's prettier than I thought.
Yes, it is.
It's so cute.
It really is.
With the German dance.
Thank you!
I used to prioritize sleeping in middle school.
Yes!
Thank you!
Thank you all for your continued support!
So, by the way...
Congratulations!
Yes, thank you!
Thank you very much!
You said you were waiting to be found
It's not gonna happen.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Youth, etch it into your heart
Tragedy is a page of comedy
Let's create the last scene
The best storytelling starts here